{
    "id": "c239f9bdbf0449f29e90c64b6f448e62",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is the church .............................. was built in the 16th century.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "John .................................. is very industrious was rewarded.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The parcel ..................................... was sent by my mother reached me this morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark ........................................ is always late for work was reprimanded by his boss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I met my uncle ........................................ had just returned from the US.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ........................................ my grandfather built.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The girls ............................................ I was speaking of have arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I know a man ......................................... wears a prosthetic leg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "whom",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard some news ..................................... disturbed me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the cat .......................................... killed the rat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}